[{ 
    "id":1,
    "question":"5*6",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"20"},{"id":2,"answer":"30"},{"id":3,"answer":"35"}],
    "rightAnswer":2
},
{ 
    "id":2,
    "question":"3*7",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"21"},{"id":2,"answer":"12"},{"id":3,"answer":"18"}],
    "rightAnswer":1
},{ 
    "id":3,
    "question":"6*8",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"47"},{"id":2,"answer":"49"},{"id":3,"answer":"48"}],
    "rightAnswer":3
},
{ 
    "id":4,
    "question":"2*9",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"11"},{"id":2,"answer":"27"},{"id":3,"answer":"18"}],
    "rightAnswer":3
},{ 
    "id":5,
    "question":"4*4",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"16"},{"id":2,"answer":"18"},{"id":3,"answer":"12"}],
    "rightAnswer":1
},
{ 
    "id":6,
    "question":"3*10",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"33"},{"id":2,"answer":"30"},{"id":3,"answer":"31"}],
    "rightAnswer":2
},{ 
    "id":7,
    "question":"1*8",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"8"},{"id":2,"answer":"1"},{"id":3,"answer":"18"}],
    "rightAnswer":1
},
{ 
    "id":8,
    "question":"0*100",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"100"},{"id":2,"answer":"0"},{"id":3,"answer":"10"}],
    "rightAnswer":2
},{ 
    "id":9,
    "question":"3*2",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"3"},{"id":2,"answer":"2"},{"id":3,"answer":"6"}],
    "rightAnswer":3
},
{ 
    "id":10,
    "question":"5*5",
    "answers":[{"id":1,"answer":"20"},{"id":2,"answer":"25"},{"id":3,"answer":"30"}],
    "rightAnswer":2
}]
